♪ CAN'T BUY ME LOVE,
LOVE ♪
♪ CAN'T BUY ME LOVE ♪
♪ I'LL BUY YOU A DIAMOND
RING MY FRIEND ♪
♪ IF IT MAKES YOU
FEEL ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ I'LL GET YOU ANYTHING
MY FRIEND ♪
♪ IF IT MAKES YOU
FEEL ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I DON'T CARE
TOO MUCH FOR MONEY ♪
♪ FOR MONEY
CAN'T BUY ME LOVE ♪
♪ I'LL GIVE YOU ALL
I'VE GOT TO GIVE ♪
♪ IF YOU SAY
YOU LOVE ME TOO ♪
♪ I MAY NOT HAVE
A LOT TO GIVE ♪
♪ BUT WHAT I'VE GOT
I'LL GIVE TO YOU ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE TOO
MUCH FOR MONEY ♪
♪ FOR MONEY
CAN'T BUY ME LOVE ♪
♪ CAN'T BUY ME LOVE ♪
♪ EVERYBODY TELLS ME SO ♪
♪ NO NO NO, NO ♪
♪ SAY YOU DON'T NEED
NO DIAMOND RINGS ♪
♪ AND I'LL BE SATISFIED ♪
♪ TELL ME THAT YOU WANT
THE KIND OF THINGS ♪
♪ THAT MONEY JUST CAN'T BUY ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE TOO
MUCH FOR MONEY ♪
♪ MONEY CAN'T
BUY ME LOVE ♪
♪ ♪
♪ CAN'T BUY ME LOVE ♪
♪ EVERYBODY TELLS ME SO ♪
♪ NO NO NO, NO ♪
♪ SAY YOU DON'T NEED
NO DIAMOND RINGS ♪
♪ AND I'LL BE SATISFIED ♪
♪ TELL ME THAT YOU WANT
THE KIND OF THINGS ♪
♪ THAT MONEY JUST CAN'T BUY ♪
♪ I DON'T CARE TOO
MUCH FOR MONEY ♪
♪ MONEY CAN'T
BUY ME LOVE ♪
♪ CAN'T BUY ME LOVE,
LOVE ♪
♪ CAN'T BUY ME LOVE, OH ♪
♪ ♪